So friends, we have reached the second week of the results season.  If you
look at this week, you will see a total of
54 companies disclosing their Quarter 4 numbers.
So let us see which company will
disclose its numbers on which date.   Let's
talk about Monday.
You will see the numbers of six companies coming on Monday.  Let's
see some familiar names.
You will also see the numbers of ICIC AMC Jal
coming on Monday.  In which
you will also see names like Swaraji.
Talking about Tuesday,
you will see the numbers of nine companies coming on Tuesday also.  If you
look at some names,
you will get the numbers of Den Network on Tuesday.
You will get the ICICI Pt Life Insurance numbers on
Tuesday.
You will find some names like Kapil Raj Novoco, Inc. in this.
Talking about Wednesday,
you will see the numbers of 13 companies coming on Wednesday.  If you
look at some names here,
you will get the numbers of HDB Financial Services on Wednesday.  ICIC LBD
numbers will come.  You will see the numbers of IDL i.e. Reliance
Industrial Infrastructure LED along with
Tejas Network
coming on Wednesday.  So all these names will be there on
Wednesday.  Let's watch together and
talk about Thursday.
You will see the numbers of 11 companies coming on Thursday.  If we
look here, the
numbers of AOK Industries will come on Thursday.
Jalel One along with HDFC AMC and HDFC L,
you will see all these names coming on Thursday.
Along with this,
you will also get the numbers for Vari renewal on Thursday and
you will see the numbers of Wipro
coming on Thursday.  And as
you know, as soon as our result season
starts, one of our
memberships gets opened by the name of Market Estimate,
where you get the
market report of the company coming out that day every morning,
through which you will know what kind of results of that company
you can see coming.  Will there
be an increase in revenue or will there be a
decline in revenue?  There will be a
rise in profit or there will be a fall in profit.
All these things are told to you in that report.
So you just think for yourself,
if I tell you this kind of information
every morning before the results are out, then
how much benefit you
can take from that information.  The charges have been kept at just
₹299 for the entire Q4 result season which will
continue for around 50 days till 29th May.
So you can understand that you will get membership of about 2 months for
just ₹299.
So this is the only group in the whole of India
where you get this kind of
information.  So come join
us and take advantage of that group.
Many people have already joined. The
link to the WhatsApp group is given in the comment box and description of the video.  You
can join from there.  Remember,
you do not need to make any payment right now.
You do
n't need to have a YouTube membership.  You do
not need to make any kind of payment.  Now you
just join the WhatsApp group.
There you will be told our UPI ID.
You just have to make
payment on that.  If we talk about 17th April i.e.
Friday, then
you will see the numbers of eight companies coming on Friday.
You will see all these names like Bajaj Consumer BMoney, Hathway Cable.   If we
talk about 18th April i.e. Saturday, then
you will see the numbers of some banks coming on Saturday.
Like HDFC
Bank numbers will come to you on Saturday.
You will also get the numbers of ICICI Bank on Saturday.
You will also see the numbers of Yes Bank and BCCL i.e. Bharat Cooking Coal Limited
coming on Saturday.  Talking about Sunday,
this time
you will not see the numbers of any company coming on Sunday.
These were the names that
you will see in focus next week
due to their results.  So if you
like the video then please like it.  Also,
please subscribe to the channel.
Thank you.